## MINJUNG KIM

💌 minjung.kim@vision.snu.ac.kr | 🎓 Google scholar | 🖸 GitHub | 🏕 minnjung.github.io

**♀** 317, Bldg 138, 1 Gwanak-ro, Gwanak-gu, Seoul, Korea

#### RESEARCH INTERESTS

My research interests are in the field of 3D Place Recognition and Visual Localization, especially about (i) understanding the scene from images and point clouds, (ii) dealing with 2D-3D cross-modalities, and (iii) utilizing high-level semantic information for place recognition.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Seoul National University

Seoul, Korea

Integrated M.S./Ph.D. Student in Computer Science and Engineering; (GPA: 4.03/4.3)

Mar. 2018 - Current

Vision and Learning lab, advised by Prof. Gunhee Kim.

#### Sogang University

Seoul, Korea

B.S. in Computer Science and Engineering; (GPA: 3.58/4.3), Magna Cum Laude Advised by Prof. Hyukjun Lee.

Mar. 2014 - Feb. 2018

## **PUBLICATIONS**

#### Indoor/Outdoor Transition Recognition Based on Door Detection

UR 2022

Seohyun Jeon, Minjung Kim, Seunghwan Park, Jaeyoung Lee

### Drop-Bottleneck: Learning Discrete Compressed Representation for Noise-Robust Exploration Jaekyeom Kim, Minjung Kim, Dongyeon Woo, Gunhee Kim

Memorization Precedes Generation: Learning Unsupervised GANs with Memory Networks

ICLR 2021

#### Logo Detection and Recognition Algorithm using YOLO-v3 Model

**CICS 2020** 

Minjung Kim, Sungen Kim, Gunhee Kim

ICLR 2018

Youngjin Kim, Minjung Kim, Gunhee Kim

#### **Machine Learning for Determining Duplicate Question**

KSC 2017

Minjung Kim, Yeongjoon Park, Hyungsuk Lim, Jihoon Yang

#### Sketch based Face Image Generation with Text Mapping

KSC 2017

Minjung Kim, Hyungsuk Lim, Yeongjoon Park, Yeseul Joo, MyoungWan Koo

#### **PROJECTS**

#### DeepGuider | GitHub

Apr. 2019 - Current

- The DeepGuider Project is a national government-funded research project focused on developing a navigation guidance system for robots to navigate urban environments without pre-mapping.
- I contribute to finding clues to locate autonomous robots by detecting and recognizing points of interests (POIs) in images of a scene, including text, landmarks, and doors for indoor-outdoor transition, while also developing robust training methods for environmental changes.

#### PRIDE: 3D Place Recognition In Dynamic Environment | GitHub

Mar. 2022 – Current

- This work proposes a new dataset called PRIDE, which includes dynamic objects such as cars and pedestrians, for 3D place recognition in dynamic environments that are more realistic and challenging than current benchmark datasets.
- The proposed PRIDE-Net architecture with a new loss function focuses on extracting discriminative global descriptors and capturing global context using spatial information, while being robust to dynamic environments.

- Experiments on the PRIDE dataset and existing benchmarks show that our proposed method outperforms previous methods and that each proposed module effectively improves performance.
- The code will be released after acceptance.

# FCAT: Fully Convolutional Network with Self-Attention for Point Cloud based Place Recognition

Dec. 2020 - Feb. 2022

- We construct a novel network named FCAT (Fully Convolutional network with a self-ATtention unit) that can generate a discriminative and context-aware global descriptor for place recognition from the 3D point cloud.
- It features with a novel sparse fully convolutional network architecture with sparse tensors for extracting informative local geometric features computed in a single pass. It also involves a self-attention module for 3D point cloud to encode local context information between local descriptors.

#### Bayesian Deep Learning course | *Lecture*

Feb. 2018 - Jul. 2018

- To understand deep learning papers, we explain the basic concepts of probability and Bayesian, and introduce papers related to Bayesian neural networks.
- This lecture can be taken through edwith of Naver Connect.

#### Sketch based Face Image Generation with Text Mapping | GitHub

Sep. 2017 - Feb. 2018

- A typical sketch might have been uncomfortable when a person or program was used to map a person's features in detail. This process is limited not only because it is very complex and requires technicians, but also because it creates a feeling of incompatibility with real people.
- This program, named Metamon, makes a picture of a person's face by entering the image of the border sketch of the person's face and the text information that shows the characteristics of the face.

#### Arduino & Raspberry Pi & Internet of Things (IoT) Tutorial | Project page

Dec. 2016 - Mar. 2017

- I create tutorial pages with Youtube videos and code for beginners in Arduino kit and Raspberry Pi development.
- I also introduce the concept of the Internet of Things (IoT) and work on a mini-project using *ThingSpeak*™.

#### Sogang Navigation and Introduction (SNI) | Github

Mar. 2015 - Jul. 2015

- We develop a navigation system that introduces the internal facilities of each building and displays the shortest route and time from building to building using the Floyd-Washall algorithm.
- To build data for the development, we measured the time taken by walking directly on each path.

#### EXPERIENCES

KDB-SNU AI course Teaching Assistant	Seoul National University <i>Apr. 2023</i>
2022-3 SK hynix ML Engineer course Teaching Assistant	Seoul National University Nov. 2022 – Dec. 2022
KDB-SNU AI course Teaching Assistant	Seoul National University  Apr. 2022 – May. 2022
LG AI core human resource training course Teaching Assistant	Seoul National University <i>Feb. 2022</i>
loT · Artificial Intelligence · Big Data (IAB) course Teaching Assistant	Seoul National University Sep. 2018 – Jun. 2019
Bayesian Deep Learning course Publisher	Naver Connect Feb. 2018 – Jul. 2018
Vision and Learning Laboratory Research Intern	Seoul National University  Jul. 2017 – Feb. 2018
Biointelligence Laboratory Research Intern	Seoul National University Sep. 2016 – Feb. 2017
Arduino & Raspberry Pi Kit Developer  Development Intern	MakeWith (Startup) Dec. 2016 – Jan. 2017

#### AWARDS & SCHOLARSHIPS

**Animal Datathon Korea** 

Animal Tech Korea

Predicting joint coordinates of a cow for pose estimation; 2nd place

Jul. 2021

Samsung Humantech Paper Award

Samsung Electronics

Signal Processing section; Silver prize

Feb. 2021

KSC 2017 Paper Award

Korean Institute of Information Scientists and Engineers

The undergraduate/junior thesis contest award

Feb. 2018

Magna Cum Laude Honor

Sogang University

Academic Honors

Feb. 2018

**Academic Excellence Scholarship** 

Sogang University

Academic Honors

Jul. 2017 - Feb. 2018

Windows 10 IoT Core & Microsoft Azure for Microsoft IoT Solution Competition

Microsoft

Implementing Internet of Things (IoT) projects with Windows 10 IoT Core and Microsoft Azure; 10th place

Apr. 2017

#### SKILLS

**Programming:** Python, C, C++

**Frameworks:** Pytorch, TensorFlow/Keras **Tools:** Git, VSCode, Vim, Docker, Slurm

Others: Arduino, Rapsberry Pi

#### PROFESSIONAL ACTIVITES

#### Reviewer of international conferences

- IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV) 2023
- IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR) 2023
- Asian Conference on Computer Vision (ACCV) 2022
- International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR) 2022, 2023
- Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS) 2021, 2022, 2023

#### **Technical Coaching**

• 2022-3 SK hynix ML Engineer Technical Coaching